Guide to the Elizabeth Gedney Christensen Gardening Collection 1822-1994
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Garden Catalogs
  - Stark (William P.) Guaranteed Trees and Plants, 1917 (Box-folder 9 / 317)
  - Stern's Nurseries, 1947; 1959 (Box-folder 9 / 318)
  - Stewart's Seed and Flower Shop, 1929 (Box-folder 10 / 319)
  - Stokes Seeds Inc., 1974; 1982 (Box-folder 10 / 320)
  - Storrs and Harrison Company, 1898; 1899; 1909 (Box-folder 10 / 321)
  - Storrs and Harrison Company, 1910; 1920; 1926; 1928 (Box-folder 10 / 322)
  - Storrs and Harrison Company, 1930; 1934; 1935; 1936 (Box-folder 10 / 323)
  - Strand's Nursery, undated (Box-folder 10 / 323.1)
  - Stumpp and Walter Co., 1924; 1930; 1941 (Box-folder 10 / 324)
  - Sunny Ridge, 1947 (Box-folder 10 / 325)
  - Sutton and Sons Ltd., 1939; 1947 (Box-folder 10 / 326)
  - Swedberg Nurseries, undated (Box-folder 10 / 326.1)
  - Sweet (George A.) Nursery Co., 1900 (Box-folder 10 / 327)
  - Swift and Co., 1940; 1951 (Box-folder 10 / 328)
  - Taylor's Herb Gardens Inc., undated (Box-folder 10 / 329)
  - Templin (L.) and Sons, 1903; 1905 (Box-folder 10 / 330)
  - Templin-Crockett-Bradley, Co., undated (Box-folder 10 / 330.1)
  - Tennessee Corporation, 1934 (Box-folder 10 / 331)
  - Thomas (C.E.) Nurseries, 1914 (Box-folder 10 / 332)
  - Thompson and Morgan, 1985 (Box-folder 10 / 333)
  - Tillinghast (Isaac F.) Seedsman and Florist, 1891 (Box-folder 10 / 334)
  - Tillinghast Seed Co., 1977; 1978; 1979; 1980; 1981; 1982 (Box-folder 10 / 335)
  - Tillotson (Will) - Roses of Yesterday, 1954 (Box-folder 10 / 336)
  - Tricker (William) Inc., 1922; 1931 (Box-folder 10 / 337)
  - Tuscon Seed Co., 1917 (Box-folder 10 / 338)
  - Tutte Bros. Nurseries, 1951 (Box-folder 10 / 339)
  - Unwin's, 1974 (Box-folder 10 / 340)
  - Van Bourgondien, 1976; 1978; 1979; 1980 (Box-folder 10 / 341)
  - Van Bourgondien, 1981-Fall; 1981-Spring; 1982-Fall; 1982-Spring; 1983-Fall; 1983-Spring (Box-folder 10 / 342)
  - Van Bourgondien, 1984-Fall; 1984-Spring; 1985-Fall; 1985-Spring (Box-folder 10 / 343)
  - Van Bourgondien, 1986; 1986-Fall; 1986-Spring (Box-folder 10 / 344)
  - Van Bourgondien, 1987; 1987-Fall; 1987-Spring; 1988; 1988-Fall; 1988-Spring (Box-folder 10 / 345)
  - Van Bourgondien, 1989; 1989-Spring; 1991 (Box-folder 10 / 346)
  - Vandenberg, 1985-Fall; 1985-Spring (Box-folder 10 / 347)
  - Van Engelen Inc., 1990; 1991 (Box-folder 10 / 348)
  - Vaughan's Gardening Illustrated Seed Store, 1893; 1894; 1898; 1923 (Box-folder 10 / 349)
  - Vaughan's Gardening Illustrated Seed Store, 1929; 1934; 1936 (Box-folder 10 / 350)
  - Vaughan's Gardening Illustrated Seed Store, 1939; 1940; 1941 (Box-folder 10 / 351)
  - Vaughan's Gardening Illustrated Seed Store, 1947; 1949; 1957 (Box-folder 10 / 352)
  - Vick (James), 1866; 1868; 1871; 1874 (Box-folder 10 / 353)
  - Vick (James), 1875; 1878; 1884-#1; 1884-#2; 1884-#7 (Box-folder 10 / 354)
  - Vick (James), 1886; 1887; 1895; 1899; 1905; 1931 (Box-folder 10 / 355)
  - Vick's Wild Gardens, 1945 (Box-folder 10 / 356)
  - Village Nurseries, 1899; 1901; 1906; 1907; 1910 (Box-folder 10 / 357)
  - Wagner Park Nursery, undated (Box-folder 11 / 358)
  - Waynesboro Nurseries, 1947 (Box-folder 11 / 359)
  - Wayside Gardens, 1971; 1978 (Box-folder 11 / 360)
  - Wayside Gardens, 1979; 1980 (Box-folder 11 / 361)
  - Wayside Gardens, 1981-Fall; 1981-Spring; 1982 (Box-folder 11 / 362)
  - Wayside Gardens, 1983; 1984; 1985-Fall; 1985-Spring (Box-folder 11 / 363)
  - Wayside Gardens, 1986-Fall; 1986-Spring; 1978; 1978-Spring (Box-folder 11 / 364)
  - Wayside Gardens, 1987-Fall; 1988-Fall; 1988-Spring (Box-folder 11 / 365)
  - Wayside Gardens, 1989-Fall; 1989-Spring; 1990; 1990-Fall; 1990-Spring (Box-folder 11 / 366)
  - Wayside Gardens, 1991; 1991-Fall; 1991-Spring; 1992-Spring (Box-folder 11 / 367)
  - Westhauser's Nurseries, 1937; 1947 (Box-folder 11 / 368)
  - White Flower Farm - Plant Book, The Garden Book; 1961; 1983; 1991 (Box-folder 11 / 369)
  - Winterthur Gift and Garden Sampler, 1987 (Box-folder 11 / 370)
  - Will (Oscar H.) and Co., 1934; 1949; 1951; 1957; 1958; 1959 (Box-folder 11 / 371)
  - Wisconsin Nurseries (W.J. Moyle and Sons), 1926 (Box-folder 11 / 372)
  - Wood (T.W.) and Sons, 1896; 1902 (Box-folder 11 / 373)
  - Young (C.) and Sons Co., 1901 (Box-folder 11 / 374)
  - Ferris (Earl) Nursery, 1946; 1959 (Box-folder 12 / 375-o.s.)
  - Field (Henry) Seed and Nursery Co. (also see Num. 130, above), 1946; 1947; 1949; 1951; 1952; 1957; 1968 (Box-folder 12 / 376-o.s.)
  - Gurney Seed and Nursery Co. (also see Num. 140, above), 1948; 1950; 1969; 1971 1977; 1978; 1989 (Box-folder 12 / 377-o.s.)
  - Shumway's (R.H.) Seeds and Bulbs, 1931; 1936; 1945; 1949; 1965; 1973 (Box-folder 12 / 378-o.s.)
  - Wesley (House of Wesley), 1983 (Box-folder 12 / 379-o.s.)
- Other publications relative to gardening.
  - The Garden Magazine, Doubleday, Page and Co., Garden City, New Jersey, 1909; 1910; 1911; 1912; 1913; 1914; 1915; 1916; 1917; 1918-19; 1920 (Box-folder 13 / 380-391)
  - The Garden Magazine, 1921; 1922; 1923; 1924; 1927; 1913; 1938 (Box-folder 14 / 392-399)
  - Country Life in America, Douibleday, Page and Co., 1906 (Box-folder 14 / 400)
  - Gardening Guide, Better Homes and Gardens, 1940; 1944 (Box-folder 14 / 401)
  - American Florist, 1890 (Box-folder 14 / 402)
  - The Country Gentleman, #1 and #2, 1864 (Box-folder 14 / 403-4)
  - Genessee Farmer, 1862; 1863 (Box-folder 14 / 405)
  - Flower and Garden Magazine, 1957 (Box-folder 15 / 406)
  - Flower Grower, intermittent, 1939-1957 (Box-folder 15 / 407-9)
  - The Home Garden, 1944 (Box-folder 15 / 410)
  - Popular Gardening, 1954-1958 (Box-folder 15 / 411)
  - Fruit Garden and Home, 1924 (Box-folder 15 / 412)
  - Gardeners' Chronicle (7 issues), 1940; 1941 (Box-folder 15 / 413)
  - The Horticulturalist, 1870 (Box-folder 15 / 414)
  - Garden Digest, 1942 (Box-folder 15 / 415)
  - Garden Flowers, 1920-1929 (Box-folder 15 / 416)
  - The Journal of Heredity, 1940 (Box-folder 15 / 417)
  - The Mayflower (John Lewis Childs) (4 issues), 1892-1904 (Box-folder 15 / 418)
  - O'Neill. Sunny O'Neill's Flower Letter, 1984 (Box-folder 15 / 419)
  - Organic Gardening and Farming, 1959 (Box-folder 15 / 420)
  - The Old Farmers ALmanac, 1945 (Box-folder 15 / 421)
  - Philadelphia Society for Promoting Agriculture, 1822 (Box-folder 15 / 422)
  - Queens' County Agricultural Society, 1861 (Box-folder 15 / 423)
  - Louisiana Weekly Market Bulletin, 1967 (Box-folder 15 / 424)
  - Michigan Farmer, 1929 (Box-folder 15 / 425)
  - Minnesota Horticultural Society, 1922 (Box-folder 15 / 426)
  - Minnesota Horticulturist, Jan. 1916 - June 1917 (Box-folder 15 / 427)
  - Minnesota Horticulturist, July 1917 - March 1918 (Box-folder 15 / 428)
  - Minnesota Horticulturist, Jan. 1919 - Sept. 1919 (Box-folder 15 / 429)
  - Minnesota Horticulturist, Oct. 1919 - May 1921 (Box-folder 15 / 430)
  - Minnesota Horticulturist, Jan. 1922 - Dec. 1923 (Box-folder 16 / 431)
  - Minnesota Horticulturist, Jan. 1924 - Dec. 1924 (Box-folder 16 / 432)
  - National Sweet Pea Society, 1945-1950 (Box-folder 16 / 433)
  - University of California, Berkeley, Rose Culture, 1950 (Box-folder 16 / 434)
  - University of California, Santa Barbara, Bulletins, 1957- 1961 (Box-folder 16 / 435)
  - University of Idaho, Snap Beans, 1960 (Box-folder 16 / 436)
  - University of Minnesota, Bulletins, 1896 (Box-folder 16 / 437)
  - University of Minnesota, Bulletins, 1897; 1898 (Box-folder 16 / 438)
  - University of Minnesota, Bulletins, 1899; 1900 (Box-folder 16 / 439)
  - University of Minnesota, Bulletins, 1905; 1906 (Box-folder 16 / 440)
  - University of Minnesota, Bulletins, 1913; 1914; 1915 (Box-folder 16 / 441)
  - University of Minnesota, Bulletins, 1934; 1935; 1936; 1947 (Box-folder 16 / 442)
  - Washington State University, Organic Gardening, 1973 (Box-folder 16 / 443)
  - United States Department of Agriculture, Bulletins, (12 items) (Box-folder 16 / 444)
  - National War Garden Commission, 1919 (Box-folder 16 / 445)
  - Agricultural Conservation Program, Santa Barbara County, 1973 (Box-folder 16 / 446)
  - California Department of Fish and Game, 1955 (Box-folder 16 / 447)
  - Unidentified Fragments (Box-folder 16 / 448)
  - Scrapbooks of clippings on gardening, 6 vols., 1934-1936 (Box-folder 17-18 / 449-454)
  - Manuscript: Of Seed Catalogs and Companies, by Elizabeth Gedney Christensen., 1995 (Box-folder 18 / 455)
  - Reprint: Bess Gedney Christensen, Japanese Imperial Morning Glories, Pacific Horticulture., Fall 1989 (Box-folder 18 / 455)
  - List of collection, by Elizabeth Christensen., undated (Box-folder 18 / 455)